<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hiragana_Homepage</string>
    <string name="ahab">Speak not to me of blasphemy man! I\'d strike the sun if it insulted me</string>
    <string name="mnemonic_a">Placeholder Mnemonic Text</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="what_next">Congratulations! You\'ve now studied all 46 Hiragana. No small achievement!
        \n So, what next? You can continue to review the Hiragana here, until you feel completely comfortable with all of them.
        We would also recommeding that you check out some of the other great Japanese learning resources out there, so that you
        can start to see Hiragana in context, build your reading fluency and begin learning you first Japanese vocabulary!
        For more in-depth advice, why not visit the Information page!
    </string>
    <string name="doneByDeadline">Congratulations! You\'ve now studied all 46 Hiragana, and not only that
        you\'ve done it by the deadline you set yourself! Well done, that\'s no small achievement!
        \n So, what next? You can continue to review the Hiragana here, until you feel completely comfortable with all of them.
        We would also recommeding that you check out some of the other great Japanese learning resources out there.
        For more in-depth advice, why not visit the Information page! </string>
    <string name="infoRecommendedMaterials">Placeholder</string>
    <string name="infoStrugglingSimilar">Placeholder</string>
    <string name="infoStrugglingListening">Placeholder</string>
    <string name="infoWriting">Placeholder</string>
    <string name="infoWhatNext">Placeholder</string>

    <string name="title_welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="title_audio">Are you able to listen to audio?</string>
    <string name ="title_otherMats">Is this the only way you\'re studying?</string>
    <string name="title_time">Do you have enough time?</string>
    <string name="title_conclusion">Let\'s get started!</string>


    <string name="desc_welcome">\n Welcome to our Hiragana app! We look forward to learning with you.
        \n\n Just before we begin, there\'s a few quick things we want to make you aware of…</string>
    <string name="desc_audio">
    \n While it is possible to complete the activities without audio, we would always recommend that
    you listen as you study, to better grasp the pronunciation of the different Hiragana.</string>
    <string name ="desc_otherMats">\n We recommend using this app in conjunction with other Japanese
    learning apps. Since we\'re only covering Hiragana here, we would strongly advise using our app
    in conjunction with a broader Japanese learning app. That way, you\'ll be seeing Hiragana in complete
    words from the beginning! </string>
    <string name="desc_time">\n While there are only 46 Hiragana, compared with thousands of Kanji,
    it is still important to note that it may take a couple of weeks of daily study before you\'ve really
    got them hammered down. \n\n Don\'t be afraid to focus on other areas of the language that you\'re
    struggling with now, and come back here when you\'re feeling ready!</string>
    <string name="desc_conclusion">\n With that out of the way, let\'s get started on learning!
    \n\n Check out the info page if there\'s anything else you need help with.
    \n\n がんばってね！</string>

</resources>